ILR School Extension Division Metropolitan District Office (New York, N.Y.) Training Manuals /4296
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Extension Division Metropolitan District Office (New York, N.Y.) Training Manuals
1988-2004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
Acevedo, Ed
Grabelsky, Jeffery
/4296
1.94 cubic feet
1.9 linear ft.
Manuals (instructional materials).
8823384
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, January 10, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 05, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3019: ILR School Metropolitan District Selected Documents /4026: ILR School Metropolitan Office Extension Division Completed Questionnaires on Union Activity /4068: ILR School Extension Division Metropolitan District Office, Anne Nelson Papers /4257: ILR School Metropolitan District Selected Files /4266m: ILR School Metropolitan District Levi Strauss files /4268: ILR School Metropolitan Office Records /4296 AV: ILR School Extension Division Metropolitan District Office (New York, N.Y.) Training Audio-Visual Materials
Employees--Training of; Acebedo, Ed; Grabelsky, Jeffery; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Extension Division. Metropolitan District Office
8823384
- Mostly IBEW manuals. (Box 1)
  - 7 Hour Training - IBEW (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Anti-Union Lawyers Notebook (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bargaining for power - SEIU, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Baustein zur Nicht-Rassistischen Bildungsarbeit (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Scope and Contents
    Section A-B
  - Baustein zur Nicht-Rassistischen Bildungsarbeit (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Section C-E
  - Building the Local Union (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - COMET - International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - COMET II (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Communities at Work (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Construction Organizers' Manual, IBEW, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Sections 1-5
  - Construction Organizers' Manual, IBEW, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Sections 6-9
  - Construction Organizers' Manual, IBEW, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Sections 10-12
  - MEMO, IBEW, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - MEMO, IBEW, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - MEMO, AFL-CIO, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - MEMO, IBEW (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - MEMO, King County Central Labor Council (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - MOVE: Training Manual, Building and Construction Trade Department, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Member Organizing Program Instruction Manual, IBEW, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    See associated VHS tape in /4296 AV
  - Numbers That Count, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Organizer's Resource Book: Construction, UBF [folder 1 of 3] (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Organizer's Resource Book: Construction, UBF [folder 2 of 3] (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Organizer's Resource Book: Construction, UBF [folder 3 of 3] (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Mostly United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners manuals. (Box 2)
  - Talking Union 1-on-1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Talking Union One-On-One (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Trainers Manual for the Comprehensive Construction Steward System [folder 1 of 3] (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Trainers Manual for the Comprehensive Construction Steward System [folder 2 of 3] (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Trainers Manual for the Comprehensive Construction Steward System [folder 3 of 3] (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Street Heat: Mobilizing to Win (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Baustin zur nicht-rassistischen bildungsarbeit (Box 3)
- MOVE (Box 4)
- Restoring every worker's right to a Voice @ Work (Box 5)
- Restoring every worker's right to a Voice @ Work (Box 6)